MUHAMAD DANANG PRIAMBODO

Full Stack Web Developer | Back End Developer

Jakarta, Indonesia | +6285710945738 | mdanangpriambodo@gmail.com | https://www.mcdanang.com/ | https://github.com/mcdanang/

SUMMARY

An engineering graduate and a Web Developer with 1+ years of experience designing, developing, and integrating front-end & back-end-based applications, Possesses knowledge of web development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Tailwind, Node.js, Next.js and some databases (MySQL, PostgreSQL, & MongoDB). Key achievement: create a full-featured responsive online grocery web application within 6 weeks, create a web application that provides a custom digital invitations for weddings and achieved high customer satisfaction.

EXPERIENCE

Final Project Full Stack Web Development Purwadhika

Full Stack Development Student (Jun 2023 - Jul 2023)

- Building a full-featured online grocery web application including authentication, authorization, product recommendation, cart, voucher discount, order management, reporting, and admin dashboard
- Designing a site map, database design, and API routing design based on project specifications
- Transforming designs into a fully responsive front-end code with React.js and Tailwind.
- Creating a REST API with Node.js and Express.js with MySQL database
- Debugging errors and troubleshoot issues.
- Check out the web app: https://jcwdolo901.purwadhikabootcamp.com/

Qurban Kuy! - Depok, Indonesia

Web Design Freelancer (May 2023 - Jun 2023)

- Creating a website for "Qurban Kuy!", a small business that sell livestock (sheep & cow) for Idul Adha Event.
- Transforming designs into front-end code with Next.js, Typescript, and Tailwind.
- Debugging errors and troubleshoot issues.
- Deploying the Next.js application to Vercel
- Check out the web page: https://qurban-kuy.vercel.app/

teman-sejati.com – Depok, Indonesia

Web Design Freelancer (Jul 2021 - present)

- Creating a web application that provides a custom digital invitations for weddings.
- Transforming designs into front-end code with Wordpress, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Debugging errors and troubleshoot issues.
- Discussing with customers to ensure the web page are aligned with customers needs.
- Achieved high customer satisfaction.
- Check my latest design: https://teman-sejati.com/dina-faiz/

EDUCATION

Purwadhika Digital Technology School (Feb 2023 -Jul 2023)

Full Stack Web Development

Institut Teknologi Bandung (Aug 2014 - Jul 2018)

Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering - GPA 3.64 (Cum Laude)

CERTIFICATIONS

- Back End Development and APIs (Node, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose) freeCodeCamp
 Relational Database (Bash, Git, PostgreSQL) freeCodeCamp
- Data Visualization (D3.js) freeCodeCamp
- Front End Development Libraries (Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, React, Redux freeCodeCamp
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (ES6, OOP, FP) freeCodeCamp
- Responsive Web Design (HTML, CSS) freeCodeCamp freeCodeCamp
- Project Management Certificate Belajarlagi
- NodeJS Backend Development with Adonis Candradimuka Jabar Coding Camp

SKILLS

- HTML
- **CSS**
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.js & Express.js
- Redux
- Redis
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB (NoSQL)
- Git & Github

- Next.js
- TypeScript
- Tailwind
- Wordpress
- Golang (beginner)
- Postman
- Scrum
- **REST API**
- Problem solving
- Team collaboration
- Scrum